RG 089, Department of Transportation
Connecticut State Library
- Series 25. Commissioner, 1941-2003, bulk 1973-2003; 88 cubic feet
  - 2002-093
    - Department of Transportation Bureau Correspondence, 1991-1994
      - Griffin Line (Box 13)
      - Guilford Transportation Industries (Box 13)
      - Housatonic Railroad Company (Box 13)
      - Increases (Box 13)
      - Metro-North (Box 13)
      - Metro Transportation Authority (Metro-North) (Box 13)
      - New Haven Rail Line (Box 13)
      - New Haven Rail Line Contingency Plan (Box 13)
      - Shoreline East (Box 13)
      - Bureau of Engineering and Highways, 1992-1993 (Box 21)
      - Bureau of State Traffic Commission, 1992-1994 (Box 21)
      - Bureau of Finance and Administration, 1990-1992 (Box 21)
      - Bureau of Engineering and Highways, 1991 (Box 22)
      - Federal Highway Administration, 1991-1993 (Box 22)
      - Bureau of Public Transportation, 1991-1993 (Box 22)
      - Bureau of Policy & Planning, 1991-1993 (Box 22)
    - United States Government correspondence, 1991-1994
      - Congress, 1994 (Box 13)
      - Congressional hearings/meetings (Box 13)
      - Civil Rights - State of Connecticut (Box 13)
      - Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) (Box 13)
      - Federal Highway Administration (Box 13)
      - FHWA IVHS / Mobility outreach field trip, 1991 September 24-25 (Box 13)
      - Federal Railway Administration (Box 14)
      - Federal Transit Administration (Box 14)
      - Transportation, United States Department of (Box 14)
      - United States Army Corps of Engineers (Box 14)
      - United States Government - general (Box 14)
    - Correspondence to Associations and Committees, 1991-1994 (Box 14)
      - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials (AASHTO) (Box 14)
      - AASHTO ballots, surveys and questionnaires (Box 14)
      - AASHTO Joint Committee on Domestic Freight Policy (Box 14)
      - AASHTO Special Committee on Economic Expansion and Development (Box 14)
      - AASHTO Standing Committee on the Environment (Box 14)
      - AASHTO Strategic Planning Task Force (Box 14)
      - AASHTO Subcommittee on Highway Transport (Box 15)
      - American Trucking Associations (Box 15)
      - The Associated General Contractors of America (Box 15)
      - Association for Bridge Construction & Design (Box 15)
      - Coalition of Northeast Governors (CONEG) (Box 15)
      - Connecticut Association of Street and Highway Officials (Box 15)
      - Connecticut Bituminous Concrete Producers Association (Box 15)
      - Connecticut Business and Industry Association (CBIA) (Box 15)
      - Connecticut Commuters, Inc. (Box 15)
      - Connecticut Energy Advisory Board (Box 15)
      - CCIA (Box 15)
      - Connecticut Engineers in Private Practice, Inc. (Box 15)
      - Connecticut Fund for the Environment (Box 15)
      - Connecticut Rail Coalition (Box 15)
      - Connecticut Road Builders Association, Inc. (Box 15)
      - Connecticut Institute - University of Hartford (Box 15)
      - Connecticut Quality Council (Box 15)
      - Council of Governors' Policy Advisors (Box 15)
      - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 15)
      - Highway Users Federation (Box 15)
      - International Bridge, Tunnel & Turnpike Association (Box 15)
      - Joint Highway Research Advisory Council (Box 15)
      - Metro District Commission (MCD) (Box 15)
      - Metro Pool (Box 15)
      - Motor Transport Association (Box 15)
      - National Governors Conference (Box 15)
      - National Transportation Safety Board (NTSB) (Box 15)
      - New England Passenger Transportation Association (Box 15)
      - New England Pollution Prevention Council (Box 15)
      - New England Transportation Consortium (Box 15)
      - North Atlantic Highway Planning Officials (Box 15)
      - Northeastern Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials (NASHTO) (Box 15)
      - Northeast Corridor Initiative, Inc. (Box 15)
      - Northeast Transit Association (Box 15)
      - Planning Agencies (Box 15)
        - Capital Region Council of Governments (Box 15)
        - Greater Bridgeport (Box 15)
        - Northeast Connecticut (Box 15)
        - Southeastern Connecticut (Box 15)
        - Southwestern (Box 15)
        - Windham (Box 15)
      - Regional Plan Association (Box 15)
      - Riverfront Recapture, Inc. (Box 15)
      - Southwestern Area Commerce and Industry (Box 15)
      - Task Force on Transportation Management Plans (Box 15)
        - Greater Bridgeport (Box 15)
        - Greater Hartford (Box 15)
        - Norwalk (Box 15)
        - Southeast area (Box 15)
      - Transportation Research Board (Box 15)
      - Women's Transportation Seminar (Box 15)
    - Subject Files, 1991-1994
      - Accent Stripe, Inc. (Box 16)
      - Affirmative Action plan (Box 16)
      - Americans with Disabilities Act (Box 16)
      - Arthur Andersen & Company (Box 16)
      - Audits (Box 16)
      - Benchmarking (Box 16)
      - Biennial budget (Box 16)
      - Bridges (Box 16)
        - Bridges, Misc. (Box 16)
        - Bridge painting (Box 16)
        - Baldwin Bridge, Old Saybrook-Old Lyme (Box 16)
        - Charter Oak (Box 16)
        - Housatonic River Bridge, Route 15, Milford & Stratford (Box 16)
        - Niantic River Bridge, East Lyme-Waterford (Box 16)
        - Peck Bridge, Bridgeport (Box 16)
        - Quinnipiac River Bridge (Box 16)
        - Tomlinson Bridge (Box 16)
        - Orphan Bridges (Box 16)
      - Budget (Box 16)
      - Budget Fiscal 1992 (Box 16)
      - Budget Federal (Box 16)
      - Buildings (Box 16)
      - Capital Program (Box 16)
      - Civil Preparedness (Box 16)
      - Claims Construction (Box 16)
      - Clean Air Act (Box 16)
      - Clean Air Act law suit (Box 16)
      - Clean Air Act Policy Committee (Box 16)
      - CMAG - Congestion Management / Air Quality (Box 17)
      - Code of ethics (Box 17)
      - Code of fair practices (Box 17)
      - Commercial drivers license program (CDL) (Box 17)
      - Public Transportation Policy Committee (Box 17)
      - Connecticut Award for Excellence (Box 17)
      - Connecticut Transit (Box 17)
      - Construction Claims Process (Box 17)
      - Consultant selection (Box 17)
      - Consultants engineer approvals (Box 17)
      - Consultant selection panel (Box 17)
      - Consultants, misc. (Box 17)
      - Consultant prequalification (Box 17)
      - Contract compliance (Box 17)
      - Contractors (Box 17)
      - Contractor prequalification regulations (Box 17)
      - Contracts (Box 17)
      - Correspondence procedures (Box 17)
      - Connecticut executive management (Box 17)
      - Connecticut Academy of Science and Engineering (Box 17)
      - Credit audit billing report (Box 17)
      - Delegation of authority (Box 17)
      - Disadvantaged Business Enterprise/Women Business Enterprise (DBE/WBE) (Box 17)
      - Della Construction Co., Inc. (Box 17)
      - Divisible load permits (Box 17)
      - Dept. of Transportation daycare center (Box 17)
      - Drunken Driving Task Force (Governor Rowland's) (Box 17)
      - Electrical Contractors, Inc. (Box 17)
      - Economic Stimulus Program (Box 17)
      - Education (Box 17)
      - Emergency declaration (Box 17)
      - Employee Commute Option Program (ECO) (Box 17)
      - Empowerment zones (Box 17)
      - Encroachment permits (Box 17)
      - Enforcement of Dept. of Transportation construction projects (Box 17)
      - Enhancement projects (Box 17)
      - Environmental permits (Box 17)
      - Equipment (Box 17)
      - Fatalities (Box 17)
      - Federal aid (Box 17)
      - Geographic information (Box 17)
      - Goals & critical success factors (Box 17)
      - Governor's care & share (Box 17)
      - Guide railing (Box 17)
      - Hartford paving (Box 18)
      - Hartford camera system (Box 18)
      - Highway safety (Box 18)
      - Human resource plan (Box 18)
      - Incident management (Box 18)
      - Intelligent vehicle highway system (Box 18)
      - Intermodal Surface Transportation Efficiency Act of 1991 (Box 18)
      - Job postings (Box 18)
      - Legislation (Box 18)
      - Lego World (Box 18)
      - Level playing field (Box 18)
      - L & C flashing barricades (Box 18)
      - Logo signing (Box 18)
      - Management incentive plan (Box 18)
      - Managers meeting/directives (Box 18)
      - Master transportation plan (Box 18)
      - Media interviews (Box 18)
      - Monthly financial statements (Box 18)
      - National Transit Safety Board (Box 18)
      - New England transportation initiative (Box 18)
      - New England Welding Contractors, Inc. (Box 18)
      - Northeast corridor improvement project (Box 18)
      - Occupational health (Box 18)
      - Organization (Box 18)
      - Overhanging trees (Box 18)
      - Parking policy (Box 19)
      - Partnering (Box 19)
      - Pavement management (Box 19)
      - Pavement markings (Box 19)
      - Perma-patch (Box 19)
      - Personnel - general (Box 19)
      - Personnel - position approvals (Box 19)
      - Regional housing meetngs (Box 19)
      - Resurfacing programs (Box 19)
      - Ridesharing (Box 19)
      - Savings bond campaign (Box 19)
      - Scenic byways (Box 19)
      - Scenic Road Advisory Committee (Box 19)
      - School bus - livery service (Box 19)
      - Security (Box 19)
      - Senior Executive Service Board (Box 19)
      - Signs (Box 19)
      - Small Business Set Aside Program (Box 19)
      - Snow & ice removal (Box 19)
      - Special tax obligation bond (Box 19)
      - Speed limits (Box 19)
      - Storms (Box 19)
      - United Way (Box 19)
      - Tolls (Box 19)
      - Tomasso, George A. (Box 19)
      - Total Quality Management (TQM) (Box 19)
      - Town aid (Box 19)
      - Transportation demand management (Box 19)
      - Travel authorizations (Box 19)
      - Tri-state Governors' meeting, 1993 May (Box 19)
      - Truck weights / safety (Box 19)
      - Unions - general (Box 19)
      - Connecticut Employees Union Independent (Box 19)
      - Urban Mass Transit Act (Box 19)
      - Urban Strategy (Box 19)
      - Vanpooling (Box 19)
      - Voluntary leaves (Box 19)
      - Worker's compensation (Box 19)
    - Correspondence to Congress, 1991-1993 (Box 20)
  - 2004-021
    - Correspondence to State Legislators, 1995-1998
      - Various Legislators (sent to more than two) (Box 1)
      - Correspondence to State Senators, Districts number 1-36 (Box 1)
      - Correspondence to State Representatives
        - Districts number 2-134 (Box 2)
        - Districts number 135-151 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence to town officials and constituents, 1995-1998 (Box 3)
      - Andover - Hampton (Box 3)
      - Hartford - Salisbury (Box 4)
      - Swymour - Woodstock (Box 5)
    - Correspondence to other states, 1995-1998 (Box 6)
    - Interdepartment correspondence, 1995-1998
      - Adjutant General - Governor's Office, 1998 July-December (Box 7)
      - Adjutant General (Box 7)
      - Administrative Services (Box 7)
      - Attorney General (Box 7)
      - Auditors of Public Accounts (Box 7)
      - Agriculture (Box 7)
      - Bond Commission (Box 7)
      - Central Connecticut State University (Box 7)
      - Comptroller (Box 7)
      - Connecticut Development Authority (Box 7)
      - Connecticut Economic Conference Board (Box 7)
      - Connecticut Public Transportation (Box 7)
      - Corrections, Department of (Box 7)
      - Eastern Connecticut State University (Box 7)
      - Economic & Community Development (Box 7)
      - Environmental Protection (Box 7)
      - Ethics Commission (Box 7)
      - Federal Funds Advisory Council (Box 7)
      - Finance Advisory Commission (Box 7)
      - Fiscal Analysis (Box 7)
      - General Assembly (Box 7)
      - General Assembly - Appropriations Committee (Box 7)
      - General Assembly - Legislative Program Review & Investigations Committee (Box 7)
      - Governor's Office (Box 7)
        - 1998 January-June (Box 7)
        - 1998 July-December (Box 7)
        - E-mail, 1998 (Box 8)
        - 1997 (Box 8)
        - 1996 (Box 8)
        - 1995 January-June (Box 8)
        - 1995 July-December (Box 8)
        - Lt. Governor's Office (Box 8)
        - Governor's Washington Office (Box 8)
        - Governor's Southern & Eastern Office (Box 8)
        - Annual Administrative Reports (Box 8)
      - Health, Department of (Box 8)
      - Human Rights & Opportunities, Commission on (Box 8)
      - Insurance Department (Box 8)
      - Information Technology, Department of (Box 8)
      - Labor, Department of (Box 9)
      - Library (Box 9)
      - Mental Retardation, Department of (Box 9)
      - Motor Vehicles, Department of (Box 9)
      - Policy and Management, Office of, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Public Safety, Department of (Box 9)
      - Public Health and Addition Service (Box 9)
      - Public Utilities Control Authority (Box 9)
      - Public Works, Department of (Box 9)
      - Revenue Services (Box 9)
      - Secretary of the State (Box 9)
      - Social Services, Department of (Box 9)
      - Southern Connecticut State University (Box 9)
      - State Properties Review Board (Box 9)
      - State Treasurer, Office of (Box 9)
      - States Attorney (Box 9)
      - University of Connecticut (Box 9)
      - Veterans' Affairs, Department of (Box 9)
    - Interdepartment correspondence, 1991-1994
      - Governor's Office, 1991-1994; 3 folders (Box 17)
      - Attorney General's Office, 1991-1993; 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Department of Transportation Bureau Correspondence, 1995-1998
      - Finance & Administration, Bureau of (Box 10)
      - Affirmative Action (Box 10)
      - Aviation (Box 10)
      - Ports (Box 10)
      - Connecticut Coastline Port Authority (Box 10)
      - State Pier (Box 10)
      - Commissioner's memoranda (Box 10)
      - Deputy Commissioner's memoranda (Box 10)
      - Communication, Director of (Box 10)
      - Engineering & Highway Operations, Bureau of, 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Engineering & Highway Operations, Bureau of (Box 11)
      - Policy & Planning, Bureau of (Box 11)
      - Maintenance (Box 11)
      - Rights of way (Box 11)
      - Public Transportation, Bureau of (Box 11)
      - Bradley International Airport (Box 11)
      - Bradley International Airport Commission (Box 11)
      - Groton/New London Airport (Box 11)
      - Amtrak (Box 11)
      - Conrail - Consolidated Rail Corporation (Box 11)
      - Increases (Box 11)
      - Griffin Line (Box 11)
      - Green Line Corridor major investment study (Box 11)
      - Metro-North (Box 11)
      - Metro Transportation Authority (Metro-North) (Box 11)
      - New Haven - Hartford Rail Line (Box 11)
      - New Haven Rail Yard, Program management plan, 1996 July 12; 1 book (Box 11)
      - Shore Line East (Box 11)
      - Waterbury Branch (Box 11)
    - United States Government Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 11)
      - Congress, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
      - Congress, 1997-1998 (Box 12)
      - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers (Box 12)
      - U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (Box 12)
      - Federal Aviation Administration (Box 12)
      - Federal Highway Administration (Box 12)
      - Federal Railway Administration (Box 12)
      - Federal Transit Administration (Box 12)
    - Correspondence to Associations and Committees, 1995-1998 (Box 12)
      - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials (AASHTO) (Box 12)
      - AASHTO ballots, surveys and questionnaires (Box 12)
      - American Public Transit Association (Box 12)
      - Associated General Contractors of Connecticut, Inc. (Box 12)
      - Association for Bridge Construction and Design (Box 12)
      - Coalition of Northeast Governors (CONEG) (Box 12)
      - Central Connecticut Transportation Association (Box 12)
      - Connecticut Association of Street and Highway Officials (Box 12)
      - Connecticut Bituminous Concrete Producers Association (Box 12)
      - Connecticut Business and Industry Association (CBIA) (Box 12)
      - Connecticut Construction Industries (Box 12)
      - Connecticut Road Builders Association, Inc. (Box 12)
      - Connecticut Institute, University of Hartford (Box 12)
      - Institute of Transportation - Engineers (Box 12)
      - Motor Transport Association (Box 12)
      - National Governors' Association Safety Board (NTSB) (Box 12)
      - New England Association of Regional Councils (Box 12)
      - New England Transportation Consortium (Box 12)
      - Northeast Alternative Vehicle Consortium (Box 12)
      - Northeastern Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials (NASHTO) (Box 12)
      - Northeast Corridor Initiative (Box 12)
      - Northeast Transit Association (Box 12)
      - Regional Planning Agencies (Box 12)
        - Central Naugatuck Valley (Box 12)
        - Greater Bridgeport (Box 12)
        - Southeastern Connecticut (Box 12)
        - Southwestern (Box 12)
        - Southwestern Area Commerce & Industry Association of Connecticut (SACIA) (Box 12)
        - Greater Bridgeport (Box 12)
        - Greater Hartford (Box 12)
        - Greater Waterbury Transit District (Box 12)
        - Norwalk (Box 12)
        - Southeast Area (SEAT) (Box 12)
      - Transportation Research Board (Box 12)
      - Women's Transportation Seminar (Box 12)
      - Connecticut Resource Recovery Authority (CRRA)
        - Board minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
        - Board minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 14)
    - Subject Files, 1995-1998
      - Affirmative Action plan (Box 15)
      - Audits (Box 15)
      - Orphan Bridges (Box 15)
      - Budget (Box 15)
      - Campaigns (Box 15)
      - Code of Ethics (Box 15)
      - Code of Fair Practices (Box 15)
      - Public Transportation Policy Committee (Box 15)
      - Connecticut Award for Excellence (Box 15)
      - Connecticut Transit (Box 15)
      - Consultant, Miscellaneous (Box 15)
      - Consultant prequalification (Box 15)
      - Consultant selection panel (Box 15)
      - Consultant engineer approval (Box 15)
      - Delegation of authority (Box 15)
      - Drunken Driving Task Force (Governor Rowland) (Box 15)
      - Emergency declaration (Box 15)
      - Equipment (Box 15)
      - Federal aid (Box 15)
      - Infrastructure improvement fund (Box 15)
      - Intermodal Surface Transportation Efficiency Act of 1991 (Box 15)
      - Managers (Box 15)
      - Master Transportation Plan (Box 15)
      - Neighborhood revitalization zones (Box 15)
      - New England Chamber of Commerce (Box 15)
      - Northeast Corridor Improvement Project (Box 15)
      - Operation Lifesaver (Box 15)
      - Overtime pending (Box 15)
      - Overtime approved, 1993-1998 (Box 15)
      - Overtime approved, 1991-1992 (Box 15)
      - Perma-patch (Box 16)
      - Project agreements Public Affiliates Program Center for Transportation (Box 16)
      - Studies - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 16)
      - Public Affiliates Program (Box 16)
      - Special tax obligation bond (Box 16)
      - Transportation Control Measures (TCM) (Box 16)
      - Telephones (Box 16)
      - Total Quality Management (TQM) (Box 16)
      - ODD Files (Box 16)
        - Bridgeport, 1991-1992 (Box 16)
        - Standardization Committee, 1991; 2 files (Box 16)
  - 2007-038
    Commissioners James Sullivan, James Byrnes, Stephen Korta.
    - Transportation Strategy Board, 2002 July - December 17 (Box 1)
    - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials (AASHTO) - Excellence Advisory Board - James Byrnes, Jr. (Box 1)
    - Northeastern Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials (NASHTO) - James Byrnes, Jr., President (Box 1)
    - Standing Committee on Highways (SCOH) Reorganization Task Force (Box 1)
    - National Cooperative Highway Research Program (Box 1)
      - Project 15-25 (Box 1)
      - Project 20-07 / 169 (Box 1)
      - Project 20-58 (04), Washington, D.C., 2008 November 7-8 (Box 1)
      - Project 20-36, Washington, D.C., 2003 November 4-5 (Box 2)
      - Project 20-7/144 - Environmental Streamlining Report (Box 2)
    - Dialogue with auto industry conference call, 2003 December 15 (Box 2)
    - James Adams, Deputy Commissioner (Box 2)
      - Biography (Box 2)
      - Signature for Harry Harris (Public Transportation), 2004 (Box 2)
      - Bradley construction, 2001 (Box 2)
      - Snow Valley International (Ski Mountain) South Windsor (Box 2)
      - James a. Adams letter to Mr. William Tomasso regarding Economic development & operation of a twenty-four acre site at Bradley International Airport, Windsor Locks, Conn., 1999 February 22 (Box 2)
      - Cellular report: beepers, IPAC, Nextel (Box 3)
      - Mileage report (Box 3)
      - Speaking remarks, 2002 May 15 (Box 3)
      - Invitations responses file started, 2004 June (Box 3)
      - Thank you notes / letters (Box 3)
      - Aviation & Ports - Bradley Airport (Box 3)
      - Bradley Union (Box 3)
      - Munsons (Box 3)
      - Northwest Airlines (Box 3)
      - Paradise Shops (Box 3)
      - Sikorsky Airport (Box 3)
      - Windham Airport (Box 3)
      - Communications (Box 3)
      - Bradley File (Box 3)
      - Bradley Working Group (Box 3)
    - Correspondence to State Legislators, 1998-2003
      - Various Legislators (sent to more than two) (Box 4)
      - Correspondence to State Senators, Districts number 1-36 (Box 4)
      - Correspondence to State Representatives (Box 4)
        - Districts number 1-54 (Box 4)
        - Districts number 55-151 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence to town officials and constituents, 1998-2003 (Box 5)
      - Andover - Groton (Box 5)
      - Guilford - Stafford (Box 6)
      - Stamford - Woodstock (Box 7)
    - Correspondence to other states, 1998-2003 (Box 7)
    - Interdepartment correspondence, 1998-2003 (Box 7)
      - Administrative Reports to the Governor, Digest of, 1999, 2002-2003 (Box 7)
      - Agriculture, Department of (Box 7)
      - Administrative Services, Department of (Box 7)
      - Auditors of Public Accounts (Box 7)
      - Attorney General (Box 8)
      - Board of Education / Services for the Blind (Box 8)
      - Chief State's Attorney (Box 8)
      - Children & Families (Box 8)
      - Commission on the Arts (Box 8)
      - Civil preparedness (Box 8)
      - Commission of Official Legal Publication (Box 8)
      - Core-CT (Box 8)
      - Connecticut Economic Conference Board (Box 8)
      - Connecticut Public Transportation Commission (Box 8)
      - Connecticut Resources Recovery Authority (Box 8)
      - Consumer Protection (Box 8)
      - Eastern Connecticut State University (Box 8)
      - Economic Development (Box 8)
      - Education, Department of (Box 8)
      - Environmental Commission (Box 8)
      - Fiscal Analysis (Box 8)
      - Freedom of Information Commission (Box 8)
      - General Assembly - Legislative Management (Box 8)
      - General Assembly - Legislative Program Review & Investigations Committee (Box 8)
      - Governor's Domestic Preparedness (Senior Steering Council) (Box 8)
      - Governor's Screening Committee (Box 8)
      - Governor's Washington Office (Box 8)
      - Governor's Southern & Eastern Office (Box 8)
      - Higher Education (Box 8)
      - Information Technology, Department of (Box 8)
      - Labor, Department of (Box 8)
      - Library (Box 8)
      - Mental Health, Department of (Box 8)
      - Mental Retardation, Department of (Box 8)
      - Military Department (Box 8)
      - Motror Vehicles, Department of (Box 8)
      - Permanent Commission on Status of Women (Box 8)
      - Policy & Management, office of (OPM) (Box 8)
      - Public Health & Addiction Services (Box 9)
      - Public Safety, Department of (Box 9)
      - Public Utilities Control Authority (Box 9)
      - Public Works, Department of (Box 9)
      - Secretary of the State (Box 9)
      - Social Services, Department of (Box 9)